我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
被困在孤岛上5年以来
我只有一个目标...活下去
For 5 years,I was stranded on an
island with only one goal... Survive.
Oliver Queen还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.
现在 我要完成我父亲的夙愿
Now I will fulfill my
father's dying wish...
根据他留给我的名单
除掉那些毒害我城市的人
to use the list of names he left me and
bring down those who are poisoning my city.
为了完成目标 我必须扮成别人
To do this,I must become someone else.
我必须掩盖身份
I must become something else.
绿箭侠 前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...
你好 我找Hall警探
听说他是副警长
Hi,I'm looking for Detective
Hall. I was told he works in Vice.
Oliver
Oliver?
McKenna Hall
McKenna Hall.
我常给人惊喜
I live to surprise.
- 我要找到Walter
- 我继父
- I want to find Walter.
- My stepfather.
我会帮你找到他 就这样
I'll help you rescue him,but that's it.
这是我的要求
That's my offer.
行
Ok.
Jerry
Jerry.
Jerry 你没事吧 看上去有点虚啊
Jerry,you ok? You look
a little peaked,man.
没事 Hill女士要我们
把狮龙转移到地下室
I'm fine. It's,uh,Mrs. Hill wants us
to move the Sherwood into the vault.
现在吗 大白天的
Now? It's mid-day.
我知道 她说有安全威胁
I know. She says it's a security threat.
最近抢劫案很多
It's,uh,all the robberies lately.
把这个拿下来行吗
Take this thing off me,all right?
我照你说的拿到了 给
I got it like you asked. Here.
快解开
Take it off me!
你唬弄我吗 这玩意儿会炸了吗
Were...were you... were you bluffing?
I mean,would the thing have detonated?
要炸会很厉害 不过不用担心
Violently. Don't worry,though.
你完全按我说的做了
所以你不会有感觉
You did exactly as I asked,so
it's just unconsciousness for you.
不会有感觉
Unconscious?
今晚你要除掉名单上一个人的话
你得放松一下
You might want to take it easy if you plan
on taking someone off that list tonight.
这就是我放松的方式
This is me taking it easy.
今晚是哪个幸运儿
So who's our lucky guy tonight?
Ken Williams 他非法传销数百万
Ken Williams. His pyramid
scheme stole millions.
人们不但没了家 他们的生活也被毁了
People didn't just lose their
homes. Their lives are ruined.
你们早点走吧 我不想搞太麻烦
Why don't you call it in early
tonight,I'm not expecting much trouble.
- Felicity 是不是你...
- 电脑改了你的锁
- Felicity! Did you just...
- Computer override your lock.
- 也许改了点
- 你这是干嘛
- Maybe a little.
- What are you doing?
我查了Williams的一些信息
I pulled up some
information on Mr. Williams.
你知道他是一个10岁男孩的单身父亲吗
Did you know he's a widowed
father of a 10-year-old boy?
我说过我只是来帮你找Walter的
I told you. I'm only
in this to help Walter.
不是和你同谋让孩子失去父母的
Not to be an accessory
to orphaning little kids.
我只是去警告他一下
I'm just giving him a warning.
你有没有想过真的为这个城市行点善
Has it ever occurred to you you
could do some real good in the city?
而不只是恢复人们的
股票投资组合和储蓄账户
Beyond just recovering people's stock
portfolios and their saving accounts.
不是只有你知道怎么重启我的系统
You're not the only one who
knows how to reboot my system.
- 我错了
- 想阻止我吗
- I made a mistake.
- Getting in my way?
- 不行
- 不是
- I don't disagree.
- No.
和你结盟 虽然只是暂时
Signing on with you. Even provisionally.
喝下去
Drink.
都是泥
That tastes like dirt.
你得喝水知道吗
You got to stay hydrated,ok?
我不缺水
Hydration is not my problem.
我的问题是用一把钝刀把子弹拿了出来
My problem is getting a bullet dug
out of my arm with a dull blade.
我看看
Let me take a look.
感染了
It's infected.
想想办法
Go figure.
好 我得阻止它扩散
Yeah,uh... I got to stop
that before it spreads.
你想在路过药店找抗生素时
When you swing past the
drugstore for those antibiotics,
再帮我买一份"箴言"或"体育画报"吗
you want to get me a copy of
"Maxim",or maybe a "Sports Illustrated"?
姚飞在山洞里有很好的草药
能治愈一切
Yao Fei had these super herbs back
in the cave that'd heal anything.
我去拿
I'm going to go get them.
你在外面呆不过一小时
You're not going to
last an hour out there.
那你就祈祷我在45分钟内回来吧
Well,I guess you better hope
I get back in 45 minutes,then.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 胖梨 Ducky 骗骗米
校对: Andrea942
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十五集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 15
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
见到你真高兴 Frank
It is so good to see you,Frank.
很久没见了
It's been far too long.
是啊 在中国呆的时间比我想的要长
Yes. My interests in China have
kept me away more than I'd like.
跟着事业走
But with The Undertaking approaching,
我想是时候回斯特林市了
I thought a return to
Starling City was in order.
Frank 其实我就想和你谈谈这事业
Actually,Frank,it's The Undertaking
that I wanted to talk to you about.
我想退出
I want to get out.
是因为Walter的事吗
Is this because of
what happened to Walter?
因为Walter 因为Robert
With Walter,with Robert.
上周我的孩子们差点失去我
Last week the Vigilante nearly
made my children orphans.
这已经是我的底线了 Frank
I've reached my limit,Frank.
你可真信任我呀 Moira
That's,uh,a lot to confide in me,Moira.
Robert也是
Robert did.
我知道他找过你
别管我应不应该知道
I know he reached out to you; whether
I was supposed to know it or not.
他有过顾虑
He had misgivings.
你们俩互相追查
He sought you out because
he knew you did,too.
但他被害了
But then he was murdered.
这对我们来说是个警告
And that should be a
cautionary tale for both of us.
我知道 我一直忍到现在
Yes,I know. And I've gone along with
this for as long as I can stomach it.
Frank 我们这样做
是为了修复林中空地
We started this to fix the Glades,Frank.
为了拯救城市 不是毁了它
To cure the city,not lay it to waste.
你加入是因为你女儿
You got into this because of
what happened to your daughter.
Amanda会让你怎么做呢 Frank
Frank... What would
Amanda want you to do?
也许我们得晚点再来
Well. Maybe we should come back later.
不 也许我们得等着 Oliver
这个问题很严重
No,maybe we should wait,Oliver.
This is really serious.
下一次她良心不安去报警了怎么办
What if her next attack of conscience
leads her right to the police?
她什么也不会说的
Oh,she won't say anything.
我得在和你发现我时想的一样
I know I had to make the same
calculation when you found out about me.
如果你想错了呢
And what would you have
done if you were wrong,
如果我选择联系Lance警官呢
and I decided to make a
call to detective Lance?
那我就拿箭指着你了
I would have put an arrow in you.
真的 你真会这么做
Really...really...you really
would have done that,really?
我跟自己打了赌 你们会多久过来
I had a bet going with myself on
how quickly you two would visit.
让我不要揭发你
Tell me not to reveal your secret.
看来我赢了
Looks like I won.
Felicity 其实我是来让你改变主意的
Actually,Felicity,I was hoping that
I could get you to change your mind.
昨晚我肾上腺素上脑
I was worked up on
adrenaline last night,
我并没有表现好
and I didn't exactly
put my best foot forward.
希望你现在给我机会说清楚
I was hoping you'd give me
the opportunity to do that now.
那从Ken Williams说起吧
How about you start with Ken Williams?
昨晚他也受你肾上腺素影响了吗
Did he also get to enjoy
your adrenaline last night?
不 为了让他儿子安睡
他及时把偷的钱还了
No,he returned the money that he stole
just in time to put his son to bed.
Felicity 我说了只是警告
Like I said,Felicity,just a warning...
此时我们得提醒公众
At this time,we'd like
to remind the public
由于神偷主要操控欧洲市场
that we are coordinating
our efforts with Interpol
我们在全力与国际刑警组织合作
as the Dodger operates
primarily in Europe,
他们建议我们提醒公众
and they have advised
us to warn the public
神偷有武器并且极其危险
that he is to be considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
我听说过这个人
You know,I heard about this guy.
他们叫他神偷 因为他从不亲自行窃
They call him the Dodger because
he avoids getting his hands dirty.
他用人质帮他行窃
He uses hostages to do
his stealing for him.
- 怎么做到的
- 在他们脖子上绑弹圈
- How?
- Puts a bomb collar around their necks.
去年马德里的一个人没有按他说的做
Last year,a guy in Madrid didn't
steal what the Dodger told him to,
据说被爆头了
and it took his head off. Literally.
现在斯特林市有个精神病人
And now the psycho's in Starling City?
他没在你的名单上真是糟糕
It's too bad his name's
not in your notebook.
我要搞垮的不都是名单上的人
You know,not all the people
that I target are on the list.
偶尔也有例外
Every once in a while,I
make an exception.
比如 劫持人质偷珠宝的贼
A hostage-taking jewel
thief,for example.
来帮我们一起拿下他如何
How about you help us take him down?
他迟到了
He's late.
从不
Never.
为了金融交易我开了瑞士的账户
I maintain a Swiss account
for financial transactions.
这是号码
Here's the number.
谢谢
Thanks.
我会把钱转给你的
I'll wire you the money.
如果我没搞错数字的话
Assuming I don't misplace the numbers.
我的记账有点粗糙
My bookkeeping method
is a little sloppy.
是吗
Really?
显然你认为狮龙宝石是可以偷的
Clearly you're under the impression that
you can have the Sherwood Ruby for a steal.
你是新来的
Well,you're new here in town.
在斯特林市我们没这么文雅
We're not as refined in Starling City.
我早有耳闻了
I'm getting that impression.
别担心
Don't worry.
你的人只是失去知觉
Your men are merely unconscious.
17分钟后会安然无恙醒来
In about 17 minutes,they'll wake up with the ability to turn
every other fence in this town.
但我可不是好惹的
But I'm not to be trifled with.
那我怎么办
What about me?
我不知道
I don't know.
你怎么办呢
What about you,indeed.
要抓住这个人 我们得查出他在哪
So to catch this guy,we need to
either figure out where he is,
或者他准备去哪
or where he's going to be.
你们都是这么想办法追踪目标吗
Is this really how you guys
figure out how to get your target?
边吃边谈
Over burgers and shakes?
抱歉 久等了
那边有桌无比闹腾的客人
Sorry it took me so long. I'm waiting on
a bunch of particularly rowdy customers.
用我帮你摆平他们吗
You need me to handle that?
谢谢你的好意 不用把事情闹大
I appreciate it,but I'm a pro by now.
有需要的话就叫我
I'll be here if you need me.
你女朋友吗
Girlfriend?
她算是我弟妹
No,it's my sister in law. Sort of.
Carly嫁给了Dig的弟弟
Carly was married to Dig's brother.
不过他去世了
And he passed away.
她似乎对你有好感啊
Well,looks like she's hot for you.
额 咱能接着说抓罪犯那事吗
Ah. Can we get back to
crime fighting,please?
说真的 Dig 我觉得你应该约她出去
Actually,Dig,I was thinking,you
probably should ask her out.
真的吗
Really?
你敢约McKenna 我立马就去约她
I'll do that just five minutes
after you ask out McKenna.
喔 神偷一案的警探哟
Ooh,the detective on the Dodger case.
- 你喜欢她吗
- 没错
- You have a thing for her?
- Yes.
有本事你就去约Carly啊
I don't see you asking Carly out.
Felicity 这家伙的目标是种特定珠宝
Felicity,this guy,he's targeting
a very specific type of jewel.
我们搞清原因 就能顺藤摸瓜抓到他
We figure out why,and that'll
give us the how to catch him.
我有个想法
I have an idea.
你那戴徽章的尤物说过
他们正和国际刑警组织合作
Your crush object with a badge said
they were working with Interpol.
我弄个小窃听器
Why don't I work a
couple of little tech,
你用调情分散她注意力
然后把窃听器安在她手机上
you distract her with a little flirty
flirt,slip said tech onto her phone.
然后我们就能了解她掌控的一切信息了
It'll turn into a micro transmitter,and
boom,we'll learn everything she knows.
我一般不是这么了解信息的
It's not how I typically
get my information.
你一般怎么办
How do you typically do it?
我会找到那人
I find the person.
然后用恐惧撬开他的嘴
And then I put the fear of
God into them until they talk.
不过你的办法值得一试
But we can try your way.
那个 Carly 我不想搞得很奇怪
You know,Carly,I don't
want this to,um,you know,
额 我只是想...
to come off weird or
anything,it's just...
你愿意跟我共进晚餐吗
Would you like to have dinner?
就订在今晚如何
How about tonight?
- 今晚吗
- 怎么 我们等得还不够久吗
- Tonight? What...
- We haven't waited long enough?
怎么没人告诉过我
街边的烤肉这么好吃呢
Who knew street meat
could taste so good?
我一猜你就急需逃离办公室休息一会
I had a feeling you needed
a break from the office.
Hank是我的第一个客户
Hank was my first client.
我让他儿子避免
为非己之罪受牢狱之灾
I kept his son from being sent away
for a mugging that he didn't commit.
他们怎么没奖励终身免费热狗给你呢
And how did that not score
you free hot dogs for life?
国家创新联合会保证
低收入人群受到法律保护
CNRI gives low income people
access to the legal system.
若非如此 他儿子早被送进监狱去了
Without them,his son could
have gone to prison forever.
我也有可能被送进监狱啊
I could have gone to prison,too.
他又雇不起超牛的律师为他辩护
He couldn't afford a dream
team of super lawyers.
所以我该为生在富人家而感到愧疚咯
So I'm supposed to feel guilty because
I'm lucky enough to have a rich family?
不 你确实很幸运
No. You are lucky.
但愿创新联合会会证明给你看
And hopefully CNRI will show you that.
把包还给我们 我们就不报警了
Give us the purse,and we
won't press any charges.
你说得对
Yeah,you're right.
我可真幸运啊
I really do feel lucky.
他跳过栅栏的时候钩住了
This got snagged as he
bolted over the fence.
貌似是他钱包上的链子
Looks like a chain from his wallet.
- 我以为你放弃追捕罪犯了呢
- 什么
- I thought you gave up crime fighting.
- What?
我是指你妹妹那件事 我以为...
Well,the business with
your sister. I figured...
你不会再掺乎警察的工作了
You'd stay out of police precincts.
是啊 我在新闻里看到你
Yeah,I...I saw you on
the news and I realized
我突然发现我还从未你的所作所为
向你道过谢
that I never thanked you for
everything that you did,so.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你升职了啊
So you got promoted.
升到重案组了
Major Crimes.
他们让我负责神偷的案子
And they assigned me to the Dodger case.
他威逼别人为他偷东西
He extorts people into stealing for him.
工作进展得如何
How's that going?
进展很慢啊
Slow.
你还是老样子 真好
Well... It was nice seeing you
the last time that I saw you.
是啊 能再见到你真好
Yeah. It's good seeing you,too.
就像重温过去的那些时光
It was like old times.
除了限制级的部分
Except the PG version.
这话是什么意思
How do you mean?
咱俩一向很会找乐子
Well,you and I always knew
how to have a fun time.
我最近的生活恰恰缺了点乐子
Something that's been
missing from my life lately.
你愿意跟我出来喝一杯吗
So how about a drink?
当然不是现在啊
Not now.
你愿不愿意... 我可以带你去...
Would you maybe...
I'll take you for a...
你乐意跟我吃个饭吗 McKenna
would you like to have
dinner with me,McKenna?
不知你听说了没 我在孤岛上渡过了五年
I don't know if you heard,I was
on a deserted island for five years
我对这套词已经不熟悉啊
and I am totally out of
practice with this whole...
好啊 我很乐意跟你吃晚饭
Well...well,dinner would be nice.
今天一整晚我都没事
In fact,I can make myself free tonight.
- 好的
- 嗯
- Yeah.
- Great.
我八点来接你吧
So I'll grab you at eight?
太好了
That's perfect.
- 嗯
- 就这么定了
- All right.
- Ok.
- 不在你这晃悠了 我走了
- 好
- I'm lingering. I'm going to go.
- Ok.
谁在那儿
Who's there?!
救我
Help me.
Lance
Lance.
队长 我是Hall警探
Sergeant,it's Detective Hall.
神偷的案子有了新进展
I have an update on the Dodger case.
艺术馆发现一具被一枪致命的尸体
A body was found in an art
gallery shot point blank.
现场还有其他三人
There were three other men there,
都因被高聚焦电流击中心脏而失去意识
all rendered unconscious by a highly
focused electric current to the heart.
博物馆的守卫也是如此
Same M.O. as that guard at the museum.
查清受害者身份了吗
Got an ID on the vic?
受害人名叫Cass Derenick
His name is Cass Derenick.
暂停
Pause.
Cass Derenick是谁
Who's Cass Derenick?
曾因持有被盗物品被捕
Arrest,possession of stolen goods.
曾因诈骗被捕
Arrest,conspiracy.
曾因倒卖被盗物品被提起诉讼
Conviction,attempted
sale of stolen goods.
这家伙是个买卖赃物的
This guy's a fence.
神偷要出手舍伍德红宝石
The Dodger's looking to
unload the Sherwood Ruby.
他肯定会再找黑市贩子的
Which means he'll be in
the market for a new fence.
找一个还没被杀的
One he hasn't,you know...killed.
找到那赃物贩子就能找到神偷
So we find the fence
and we find the Dodger.
我从网上看到你卖带链子的钱包
链子上还有个八号球
Anyway,I saw online that you sell a chain
wallet with an eight ball on the chain.
如果我给你外形的描述
I was wondering if you
could give me a name of
你能记起这是你的哪位客户吗
one of your customers if
I gave you a description?
没问题 你可以给我回电话
Yeah,sure,you can call be back.
就像所有我呼叫过的二手服装店一样
Like every other used clothing and
leather good store I've called today.
怎么回事
What was that about?
穿得这么帅要去干嘛啊
What's up with the fancy fancy?
我今天有个约会
What? Oh,um,I have a date.
我的生活才不像别人说的那样无趣呢
Contrary to popular
opinion,I do have a life.
你这么紧张干嘛
Then why do you seem so nervous?
很明显吗
Is it obvious?
做回那个魅力四射的你自己就好
Just be your charming and brooding self.
万千女孩都会为你着迷的
I mean,the girls seem to dig that.
我今天约的这个女孩可与众不同
This girl is different.
我在海难之前就认识她了
She knew me before the
island,before I was...
是创新联合会的电话 我必须得接
That's CNRI. I've got to take this.
我这有个很重要的手包抢劫案
I'm working on a very
important purse snatching case.
好吧
Yeah.
喂
Hello?
他穿着件红色连帽衫
Yeah,he might have been
wearing a red hoodie.
有点阿贝克隆比的感觉
Kind of Abercrombie-looking.
我是说他的脸 不是衣服
His face,not the hoodie.
真的 你们真的记得他的名字吗
Really? You wouldn't
happen to have his name?
太感谢你了
Thank you so much.
嗨 Laurel
Hey,Laurel.
你爸还喜欢抓罪犯吗
Does your dad still like arrest people?
我查出那个抢包的混蛋是谁了
I found the dirt bag.
他叫Roy Harper
His name is Roy Harper.
我都记不清上次来这里是什么时候了
I can't remember the
last time I was here.
真美啊
It's so beautiful.
想勾搭高中小女生就带她来这
Yeah,this was the place to
take a girl in high school.
我没那么幸运 能体验那些
Hmm,I was never lucky
enough to experience that.
我那时候戴着牙套 留着难看的刘海
I had braces and
terrible bangs back then.
我相信你那时一定很漂亮
I'm sure you looked amazing.
我很高兴我们终于走到这一步
I'm glad we finally got
around to doing this.
我也是
Me,too.
Andy讨好女生可有一套
You know,Andy set a pretty high
bar when it came to first dates.
他能制服一个持枪歹徒
You know,he'd face down
armed gunmen for a living
但和你约会前 我从未见过他那么慌张
but I've never seen him as scared as
he was before that first date with you.
哦 Carly 真抱歉
Ohh,Carly,I'm sorry.
初次约会不该说这些对吧
That wasn't good first
date etiquette,was it?
在咱俩正度过一个浪漫的夜晚
提起Andy 这可不太好
Bring up Andy when we are having
a romantic night? Probably not.
Carly 约会很复杂 也很艰难
Look,Carly,this is
difficult and complicated.
又没有指导手册
It's not like there's a manual,you know?
你知道吗 有一瞬间
我觉得自己就像个暗恋别人的小女生
You know... For a moment,I...I
felt like a girl who likes a boy,
剩下的都不重要
and nothing else mattered.
但如果对你来说 太难 或太复杂
But if this is too hard
for you,or too complicated,
请离开我的世界 因为我已受过太多伤害
then please,just get out now,because
I've already been hurt too much.
- Carly 听着 对不起...
- 带我回家 好么
- Carly,listen,I'm sorry...
- Can you just please take me home?
不是吧 简直太好吃了
No,no,no,no,it is not possible
for something to be this good!
是吧
Right?
- 你肯定没吃过舒芙蕾
- 什么
- So you must have missed souffles.
- What do you mean?
在岛上生活五年 远离人烟
Five years on an island,away
from civilization.
你做什么
Ah,what did you do?
吃什么 睡哪里
What did you eat? Where'd you sleep?
- 怎么熬过来的
- McKenna...
- How did you make it?
抱歉 我不是想刨根问底
Sorry. Didn't mean to drill you.
没关系
It's ok.
只是我都很久没和
It's just I haven't had a
conversation with a guy in a while
不是罪犯的男人聊过天了
without it resulting in
me reading him his rights.
但这些年 肯定改变了你
So. Yeah,but those years,they
must have changed you.
从以前和我一起狂欢 到现在这个你
From a guy I used to party
with to who you are now.
是啊
Yeah.
因为我要做些艰难的选择
Because I had to make
some tough choices.
你说得对
You're right.
我变了
It changed me.
什么艰难的选择...
What kind of tough choices...
我不想谈论这些经历 McKenna
I don't want to talk about
those experiences,McKenna.
电话解了围哈
Saved by the cell.
Hall
Hall.
把线人告诉你的写在搜查令申请中
Ok,put what the C.I. told you
in the warrant application.
我马上就到 工作上的事 我先走了
I'll be right there.
It's work,I got to go.
Felicity 听着
Felicity,listen,please.
启动McKenna手机中的监听器
I need you to activate
the bug in McKenna's phone.
警方似乎有了骗子的线索
I think the police just
got a lead on the Dodger.
好
Ok.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是Alan Durand 一名交换生
My name is Alan Durand.
I'm an exchange student.
我跟班里出去海钓
I was on a fishing
excursion with my class.
我走丢了 船失火了
We got lost and our boat caught fire.
出了什么机械故障 我们得跳船
It was some mechanic
malfunction. We had to jump ship.
什么时候
When?
两天前
Two days ago.
太糟了
It was awful.
我以为我要死了
I thought I was going to die.
其他学生呢
Where are the other students?
船员呢
Where's the boats crew,huh?
我觉得只有我活下来了
I think I'm the only one who made it.
我游到了岸边
I managed to get to shore.
以为我很幸运 但...
I thought I was lucky,but...
什么 有人找到你了么 士兵还是...
What? Somebody found you? Soldiers,or...
对
Yes! Yes.
他们头戴面具 打我
They had these masks on and
they attacked me and beat me.
把我丢在这
They left me here!
他们是谁
Who are they?!
你要是能给我松绑就好了
You can untie me at
any point,by the way.
这地方不错啊
Nice place you have here.
谢谢
Oh,thank you.
告诉我 是所有的黑货市场都要雇打手么
Tell me. Does every fence
in this town hire muscle?
一听说你对Cass Derenick的所做
我就雇了
I did as soon as I heard about
what you did to Cass Derenick.
对了 Cass啊
Oh,yes,Cass.
愿他安息
God rest his soul.
他可不是善茬
He wasn't a very nice man.
想偷我东西
He tried to steal from me. Oh.
我听说你的判断力不错
I've heard that you have
a better sense of judgment.
能转移这个
And that you have no
trouble in moving this.
这只是完璧归赵啊
Well,it's only a
recession for some people.
我收15%的佣金
I take a 15% commission off the top.
12% 行吗
Let's call it at 12,shall we?
显然不用我提醒你
Obviously I don't have
to remind you about what
上个耍我的人 下场如何
what happened to the last person
who tried to screw me over.
斯特林城刑警 手放地上
SCPD! Grab the floor!
悄悄过来
Come quietly!
恐怕我得拒绝了
I'm afraid I'll have to decline.
恐怕你不会进监狱了
Then I'm afraid you
won't be going to jail.
我听新闻说神偷逃跑了
I heard on the news the Dodger got away.
但愿今晚没白干
Hopefully the night
wasn't a complete waste.
你的约会怎样
Your dates. How'd they go?
- 很好
- 不错
- Great.
- Awesome.
你俩太不会说谎了
You two suck at lying.
我和警方破坏了神偷的交易 他没拿到钱
The police and I busted it up before
the Dodger could get himself paid.
别转移话题
Don't change the subject.
你的黑客芯片还有用吗
Is your hacker chip still working?
你俩真没劲
You two are no fun.
有 还能接受到很强的信号
Yeah. Still getting a strong signal.
你该调出警方记录
You should pull up the police records.
所有神偷偷的东西
Everything the Dodger's stolen so far.
- 你想什么呢
- 我们知道骗子
- What are you thinking?
- We know the Dodger has a taste
爱好特别种类的古物
for a very specific type of antiquity.
看起来都像凶兆十年的产物
These all look like they're
from the ominous decade.
费迪南统治的最后十年
The last ten years of
King Ferdinand's reign.
她还说我们没有无聊
And she says we have no lives.
还有没有其他地方
销售或展示凶兆的东西
Are there any other places that sell
or display items from the ominous thing?
是时期 没有
Decade. Not really.
可能斯特林城市民更喜欢伊丽莎白时代
I guess people in Starling
City prefer the Elizabethan era.
斯特林城癌症协会
The Starling City Cancer Society.
那写着明晚他们要举办募捐拍卖会
It says right there they're holding
a fundraising auction tomorrow night.
我们能引诱他去
We could lure him out into the open.
用什么引诱 赝品吗
With what? A fake?
不 神偷会知道那是赝品的
No. The Dodger clearly has a
trained eye for this sort of thing.
除了真品外 他不会上当的
He's not going to fall for anything
less than the genuine article.
咱去哪找珍贵的西班牙古物
Where are we going to get our
hands on a rare Spanish antiquity?
你是真不知道他家有多有钱 是不是
You really have no idea how
rich his family is,do you?
小Roy William Harper
Roy William Harper Jr.
大的在哪
Where's senior?
诺里斯公墓
Norris cemetery.
抱歉
Sorry to hear that.
赌马的人多了
You and an army of bookies.
我能走了吗
Can I go?
不行 你被指认为一起
钱包盗窃案的嫌疑犯
No. You've been IDed as a
suspect in a purse snatching.
你这前科可真不少啊
It's quite a resume
you've compiled here.
小偷 入室盗窃 抢劫 小偷
Petty theft,B&E,robbery,petty theft.
偷车 老变花样啊 小偷
Stolen car. Well,it's nice to change
things up once in a while. And petty theft.
你怎么不抢银行
You got something against banks?
带枪抢劫太费劲了
Well,it is hard to run
with one under your arm.
没准你在监狱里能学两招
Well,maybe you'll learn a
few new skills in prison.
听着 我不想偷窃
Look,I don't want to steal.
好么 我没别的选择
Ok? I don't have any other choice.
我妈 她...她有问题
My mother,she... She has a problem.
没错 她儿子是个傻瓜
Yeah,her son's a moron.
不是
No.
致幻剂
Vertigo.
去年她迷上致幻剂
She got hooked on Vertigo last year.
她试着戒掉 但毒瘾太深
She kicked it,but I guess
she'd done enough that...
把她折磨得不成人形
It messed her up.
她不同于从前 她的医药费账单...
She hasn't been the
same,and her medical bills...
听着 我只是想帮她摆脱困境
look,I'm...I'm just trying to
help her get out from under.
听着 我们不像那些人养尊处优
Look,we're not privileged enough
to have as much as other people.
好么
Ok?
好吧
Fine.
让他走吧
Let him go.
不就是个包包吗
It's just a damn purse,right?
他们会和你会见
They'll meet with you.
已经安排好了
It has been arranged.
谢谢
Thank you for this.
还有一件事要你帮忙
There's one more thing
I need you to do for me.
只有Malcolm知道Walter被关在哪
Malcolm's the only one who
knows where Walter's being kept.
我需要条线索
I just...I just need a clue.
有线索去追踪
Some lead to follow.
要是计划成功了
我可不想让它毁了Walter
If our plan works,I can't
let it damn Walter to hell.
不
No.
恐怕我们命该如此
That's the fate that's in
store for us,I'm afraid.
警察也到了
The police are here,too.
你的诱饵至少把他们引来了
Your bait's attracted them,at least.
这可不是我想抓的人
That's not exactly who
I'm looking to catch.
我从胸针的GPS上收到了良好的信号
So I'm getting a good signal from
the GPS I put in your family's broach.
能用手机追踪它
I can track it on my phone.
说到这 你想过如果这没用
Speaking of,have you given any
thought to what might happen
神偷还把你的珠宝卷跑了怎么办么
if this doesn't work and the Dodger
absconds with your family jewels?
不好意思 我不该这么说
I'm sorry,that came out very wrong.
仔细盯着就好 Felicity
Let's just keep our eyes open,Felicity.
那不是...
Hey,isn't that...
我还是去抓我的贼吧
I would rather take my chances
with a deadly jewel thief.
也是
Right.
胸针由Queen家族捐赠
That broach was donated
by the Queen family.
想要就得出价
If you want it,you're
going to have to bid.
宝贝 我想我可以直接拿走
Actually,love,I thought
I'd just take it.
我还是查看下前门 看安保是否正常
Maybe I should check out front,see if
the security guards had any problems.
很好 我去查看下诱饵
That's a good idea. I'm
going to go check on the bait.
我有麻烦了
I think I have a problem.
离开点 它要爆炸了...
Get away from me! If this thing blows...
不会爆的
Not going to happen.
神偷说过 报警他就会...
The Dodger said if I
called the police,he'd...
我会是无头鬼吗
I'm going to get decapitated,aren't I?
追踪器在移动
The tracker's on the move.
找到他 就让他帮你打开
If I find him,I can
get him to disarm it.
跟我说着话 要冷静
Talk me in. Stay calm.
来不及的
Too late.
去 快去
Go. Just go. Go,go,go.
说话 Felicity
Talk to me,Felicity!
朝亚当斯和奥尼尔大道去了
Heading towards Adams and O'Neil.
看速度 应该是开车的
At the clip he's going,he's
got to be in a vehicle.
嘿 借用你的车
Hey. I need your bike.
- 开玩笑吗
- 并不是
Are you kidding me? No.
我在追了 他在哪
I'm mobile. Where is he?
快告诉我 Felicity
Talk to me,Felicity.
第一次这么感谢交通摄像头
First time anyone's ever been
grateful for traffic cameras.
他离你一个街区
He's one block from your position.
若从哈里斯广场穿过去 就能追上他
If you cut through Harris
Plaza,you'll end up right behind him.
他现在在哪
Where is he now?
看到了 我看到他了
Got it. I got him,I got him.
向北的灰色轿车里 你前面那个红绿灯处
Gray sedan driving north.
At the light ahead of you.
向右急转
Ok,hard right.
别做傻事
Don't do anything stupid.
我很有预见性地给一金发妞戴了项圈
她好奇心太重了
I had the foresight to collar up
a particularly inquisitive blonde.
猜你是她朋友
I assume she's a friend of yours.
敢碰我一下 她就没命了
Touch one hair on my
head and she loses hers.
你能做出明智的选择吧
You've got quite the
choice to make,don't you?
这次不了
Not this time.
你正中动脉被切断了
Your median artery's been severed.
没法按这个键了
You couldn't push that
button if you tried.
老天
Oh,thank God.
你为何如此
Why are you doing this?
我跟你一样
I'm exactly like you.
我只劫富
I only steal from the rich.
我可不是罗宾汉
I'm not Robin Hood.
我不知道这些人什么时候回来
I don't know when these
men are coming back!
相信我 放了我 求你了
You have to believe me. Untie me,please!
难道以为他们把我当诱饵安置在这吗
What,do you think these men,they planted
me here,some kind of trap or something?
那他们干嘛绑住你 就一走了之呢
Well,why'd they tie you up like
that and then just leave you?
为什么不直接杀了你
Huh? Why not just kill you?
本来要杀的 后来被叫走了
They were going to! They
got called away at some...
因为岛上别处起了争执
some altercation somewhere
else on the island.
他们要是回来 我们全得死
If they come back,they
will kill both of us.
求你了 必须相信我
Please! You have to believe me.
求求你
Please.
好吧 转过身去 转
All right,turn... all right,turn around.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你
抱歉 不能放你
I'm sorry... But I can't.
什么 为什么
What? Why?!
为什么不能
Why not?
因为我不认识你
Because I don't know you.
你个脑残
Are you out of your mind?!
求你了
Please!
你怎么能这样 不能留我在这
You can't do this! You
can't just leave me here!
昨一整晚我都在想Andy该有多生气
You know,last night all I could think
about was how pissed off Andy will be;
看到我们在一起 会多受伤
how hurt he'll be if he saw us together.
可我若是伤害你 他会更难过 Carly
But that's nothing compared to how he'd
be if I did something to hurt you,Carly.
相信我 对我来说 约会比战争难多了
Believe me when I tell you
that war is easier than dating.
战争中 不进攻就得死
In a war,you act or you die.
不容置疑自己
No time to think,no time
to second guess yourself.
也许那就是你的问题了
Maybe that's your problem.
和我在一起 你想太多
With me,you're thinking.
却没用心感受
Not feeling.
没错
You're right.
你怎么知道我住这
How did you know where I live?
有个玩意叫互联网
A little thing called the Internet.
能开门说话吗
Look,could we not do this
with a door between us?
猜你不起诉我了 因为你觉得自己能...
So I guess you're not pressing
charges 'cause you feel like...
能改变我的人生 是吧
you feel like you can change my life?
然后再去跟那些预科有钱朋友说
And so you can run and tell
your rich prep school friends
你是多么圣洁伟大 扶贫济困
what a Saint you are and how
you're helping the disadvantaged?
你根本不了解我
You don't know a thing about me.
Thea Queen 含着金汤匙的奶娃娃
Thea Queen. Trust fund brat.
毁了作为生日礼物的汽车
Totaled her car,which she
got as a birthday present.
迷恋奢侈品 聚会过多 常上小报
Loves designer labels and is usually
in the tabloids for partying too much.
我没漏掉什么吧
Did I...did I leave anything out?
当然有
Yeah.
生父早逝 继父失踪 哥哥受伤
Dead father,missing
step dad,damaged brother,
因为车祸差点蹲监狱
and almost served jail
time for that car accident.
并且 想拿回自己的包包
Plus,she really wants her purse back.
你真是吃了豹子胆了
You know,you showed some
real sack coming down here,
半夜跑来贫民窟
the Glades in the middle of the night.
你肯定不知这复古包的价值
You must not know the
value of a vintage purse.
别担心 都在
Don't worry,it's all there.
除了这些
Except for these.
你果然有恶习
You know,it's a really
filthy habit you got there.
可不是嘛
Yeah,tell me about it.
给你点建议吧
Hey,can I give you some advice?
第一 离贫民窟远点
First,stay out of the Glades.
第二呢
And second?
别信我这种人告诉警察的悲情故事
Don't fall for every sob story
a guy like me tells the police.
祝夜生活愉快
You have a great evening now.
你不休息的吗
Do you ever take time off?
有啊
I do.
昨晚 我就去约会了
In fact,last night I went on a date.
那家伙真混蛋
The guy was kind of a jerk.
是嘛
Really?
他也许有苦衷
He might have had a reason.
McKenna 我在岛上失去的不止五年时间
McKenna,I didn't just lose
five years on the island.
我也失去享受生活的能力
I lost the part of me that
enjoyed... Being alive.
听听音乐 与美女品尝蛋奶酥
Listening to music and,uh... eating
a souffle with a beautiful girl.
本不是难事
It's the easy things.
可当你问起小岛生活
But when you asked me about the island,
就让我想起所有的艰辛
it reminded me of all the
hard things and the choices
还有不得不做的选择 都残留我心
that I have to make
that still stay with me.
让我多疑 甚至怀疑自己是否值得
Made me question how I can trust,and even
if I'm worthy of... being with anyone.
你值得拥有
You are.
请你共进晚餐可以吗
Can I take you to a dinner?
保证不中途离开
That I promise not to cut short.
去吃蛋奶酥就答应你
Um... Throw in a souffle and you're on.
McKenna
McKenna!
你还在真好
Glad you're still here.
- Queen
- Lance先生
- Queen.
- Mr. Lance.
我其实正准备走 有事吗 长官
Actually,I was just leaving.
Is everything ok,sir?
我要你一起调查义务警员
Yeah. I'd like you to,uh,work with
me on the Vigilante investigation.
是 长官
Thank you,sir.
不用担心 定能抓住他
Well,don't worry,we'll bring him in.
当然
Oh,yeah.
准备走了吗
Ready to go?
走吧
Yep.
好的
Ok.
味道真像烟灰
It tastes like an ashtray.
不过很管用
But it does the job.
我欠你人情
I owe you one.
没遇上什么麻烦吧
You didn't get into any
trouble out there,did you?
没 完全没有
No. Not a bit.
Frank Chan推荐了你
Frank Chan recommended you.
他说你能帮忙解决问题
He said you could help
us with our problem.
你能见我 他很感激
He appreciates you
agreeing to meet with me.
朋友嘛 应该的
Anything for a friend.
所以 要我们怎么帮
So... How can we be of assistance?
Malcolm Merlyn
Malcolm Merlyn.
帮我杀了他
I want you to kill him for me.